[{"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bf1", "question": "In which city's harbor would you find the statue of The Little Mermaid?", "answer": "Copenhagen", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6010c5370775fa611bce67c4", "question": "What newspaper is nicknamed \"the Gray Lady\"?", "answer": "The New York Times", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e8", "question": "What does M.C. stand for in M.C. Escher's name?", "answer": "Maurits Cornelis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d9b", "question": "Who played the role of the US president in the movie \"The American President\"?", "answer": "Michael Douglas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7ca49877e98cb97778a05", "question": "Which Asian capital was formerly known as Batavia?", "answer": "Jakarta", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe52cff1bf59ab7d2e3810b", "question": "How did IPA beer get its name?", "answer": "IPA beer was originally exported to India", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133984b", "question": "The music duo \"Daft Punk\" consists of which two French musicians?", "answer": "Thomas Bangalter and Guy-Manuel de Homem-Christo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c503", "question": "What actually is a shooting star?", "answer": "A meteor", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c332", "question": "What was the purpose of the ancient medicinal confection made from the marshmallow plant?", "answer": "To treat irritated mucous membranes and increase the flow of breast milk", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff20e7731a458464a93c423", "question": "Where did J.K. Rowling write her first novel?", "answer": "The Elephant House Cafe in Edinburgh.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7c410877e98cb9777899a", "question": "What city requires aspiring cab drivers to undergo years of training?", "answer": "London", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd66a08a5bfecdd737e087f", "question": "What was the first company to air a legal TV commercial?", "answer": "Bulova watch company", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60062b11c9d816e292245c1d", "question": "What American artist is known for word paintings?", "answer": "Ed Ruscha (His\u00a0artistic training was rooted in commercial art.)", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58ab1782baab681b09292183", "question": "What numbers appear on Donald Duck\u2019s car plate?", "answer": "313", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac9a", "question": "What is the FBI motto?", "answer": "Fidelity, Bravery and Integrity", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339332", "question": "In what year did the TV show \"The Hills\" premier on TV?", "answer": "2007", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015f858fe83fe1f2a824c2c", "question": "Under whose presidency were the waters in the fountains of the White House first dyed green in honor of Saint Patrick's Day?", "answer": "Barack Obama", "category": "history"}, {"id": "600f71efa9e54d890926f6e7", "question": "What was the original name of Austin, the capital of Texas?", "answer": "Waterloo -- It was renamed after Texas leader Stephen F. Austin in 1839.  It became the state capital in 1845.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a596", "question": "What is the geographical term for a ring-shaped coral island?", "answer": "Atoll", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c622", "question": "What element is most commonly found in Earths atmosphere?", "answer": "Nitrogen", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e9", "question": "What was writer and war hero T.E. Lawrence popularly known as?", "answer": "Lawrence of Arabia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133910f", "question": "In which Tennessee Williams' play do you encounter the character \"Big Daddy\"?", "answer": "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5909cdc8bb53d1af658864ec", "question": "What year marked the first appearance of Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer?", "answer": "1939", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdb1", "question": "Which ingredient provides the red color in a Tequila Sunrise?", "answer": "Grenadine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b49b", "question": "Which country were the 1912 Summer Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133993b", "question": "What character on the original Star Trek TV series was played by James Doohan?", "answer": "Scotty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be70", "question": "What is Michigan Stadium also known as?", "answer": "The Big House", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a3a", "question": "What type of animal was Bambi's friend Flower?", "answer": "Skunk", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef5ed26ce05a3942286e3a", "question": "What baseball legend has a cameo in \"The Benchwarmers\"?", "answer": "Reggie Jackson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59cdb6e065ff7d326b622a9b", "question": "Which baseball player was nicknamed \"The Bambino\"?", "answer": "Babe Ruth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2d1", "question": "Which 1956 film did Bing Crosby, Grace Kelly and Frank Sinatra star in?", "answer": "High Society", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cba", "question": "What TV show featured the fictional \"The Knights of the Scimitar\" fraternity?", "answer": "Cheers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c200", "question": "Which country hosted the first Olympic Games in 1896?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3fd", "question": "Who succeeded James Garfield as US President?", "answer": "Chester A. Arthur", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395fb", "question": "In the 1998 movie \"You've Got Mail\", Joe and Kelly are in what business?", "answer": "Book retailing", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600f7519a9e54d890926f704", "question": "What is zucchini called in the UK?", "answer": "Courgette -- Zucchini/courgette is a variety of cucurbit, belonging to the same family as cucumber, squash, and melon.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba55", "question": "Who coached the Chicago Bulls to their first NBA championship in 1991?", "answer": "Phil Jackson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a31", "question": "Who played the title role in the 1962 award-winning film \"Lawrence of Arabia\"?", "answer": "Peter O\u2019Toole", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae98", "question": "Who was US president when the stock market crashed in 1929?", "answer": "Herbert Hoover", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd822e5d0de9af39e9d46ac", "question": "How many vice presidents did FDR have during his time in office?", "answer": "3", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339237", "question": "What novel did Universal Studios pay Michael Crichton $2 million for before it was even published?", "answer": "Jurassic Park", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5f164ecef9b80650dbe7f938", "question": "What color is the \"Power stone\" in the 2017 Marvel Legacy relaunch?", "answer": "Purple", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd66d94a5bfecdd737e08a3", "question": "What was the most popular month for weddings in the U.S. in 2019?", "answer": "October", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6c5", "question": "What are the three main sections of an insect's body?", "answer": "The head, the abdomen and the thorax", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f7a", "question": "What was Jonathan Richman's backing band?", "answer": "The Modern Lovers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca00", "question": "What is the technical term for an organism that eats other organisms as food?", "answer": "A heterotroph", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b410", "question": "What Shakespearean king was actually king of Scotland for 17 years?", "answer": "Macbeth", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a005", "question": "In what film is Bill Murray the author of the play \"Return to Love Canal\"?", "answer": "Tootsie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f31", "question": "Which band member of Alice in Chains died of drug overdose?", "answer": "Layne Staley", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa0c", "question": "From whom did the US buy the Virgin Islands?", "answer": "Denmark", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0e1", "question": "Calamarata pasta is shaped like what?", "answer": "Wide rings", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133905a", "question": "Painter Salvador Dali was a native of which country?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b387", "question": "In which country was the first soccer World Cup held?", "answer": "Uruguay", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339158", "question": "What popular artist sang the words: \"I'm afraid of Americans\"?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b9f", "question": "Who wrote the book \"Billy Budd\"?", "answer": "Herman Melville", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6a2", "question": "On which US coast can Redwood trees be found?", "answer": "West coast", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b12", "question": "Which Lord of the Rings character has an alter ego called \"Gollum\"?", "answer": "Smeagol", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "601b4c3b49076251badbead0", "question": "Which First Lady was the first to graduate college?", "answer": "Lucy Hayes -- The wife of President Rutherford B. Hayes, she received her degree from Wesleyan Female College at the age of 18.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6012125263c99d48cd169ae1", "question": "\"Prehistory\" refers to the era before what?", "answer": "Writing -- The Prehistoric Era lasted from around 12,000 to 3,000 B.C.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c813", "question": "What unorthodox scientific belief was championed by the Universal Zetetic Society?", "answer": "A flat earth", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a78", "question": "In \"Ferris Bueller's Day Off\", what actor was listed in the credits simply as \"boy in police station\"?", "answer": "Charlie Sheen", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b71c", "question": "In what country does Santa typically sport a long coat and beard?", "answer": "England", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aff8", "question": "What were the first names of explorers, Lewis and Clark?", "answer": "Meriwether and William", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b3589ac5db0d66a186cb54d", "question": "Until 1989, what European country was the world\u2019s second largest exporter of bottled wine?", "answer": "Bulgaria", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339eb3", "question": "What slogan is painted on the nose of Robert Duvall's Wagner-blasting helicopter in \"Apocalypse Now\"?", "answer": "Death from above", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3bb", "question": "What two metals form the alloy white gold?", "answer": "Gold and silver", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd9716b23c87fd04dd15e4b", "question": "What company was the first to be valued at more than a trillion dollars?", "answer": "PetroChina", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a13f", "question": "\"Safety Dance\" was a hit for which band?", "answer": "Men Without Hats", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c736", "question": "What alloy is comprised of copper and zinc?", "answer": "Brass", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe4b51b06d333868d34d6e5", "question": "A 1634 Spanish decree called what city \"Key to the New World and Rampart of the West Indies\"?", "answer": "Havana", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9eb", "question": "Who is considered to be the creator of the \"Gran Turismo\" game series?", "answer": "Kazunori Yamauchi", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133913a", "question": "What is the full name of the fictional character Doc Savage?", "answer": "Clark Savage, Jr.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600f735ca9e54d890926f6f0", "question": "What word comes from the name of a hot spring in Iceland?", "answer": "Geyser -- The term refers to a specific geyser named Geysir, which means \"the gusher\" from the Old Norse \"geysa\" for \"to gush\".", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390e6", "question": "What year was writer Arthur C. Clarke born?", "answer": "1917", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a686", "question": "Which three states share a border with Michigan?", "answer": "Indiana, Ohio and Wisconsin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339595", "question": "In the film Moneyball who stars as the general manager of a struggling baseball team?", "answer": "Brad Pitt", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffb58bd5dad637d903c8811", "question": "The Band-Aid supergroup was formed in 1984 to raise money for famine relief in what troubled African nation?", "answer": "Ethiopia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "591c35aa815febcc896f925f", "question": "In which country would you most likely find the traditional Mariachi bands?", "answer": "Mexico", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b56b", "question": "What is Lipton the world's biggest-selling brand of?", "answer": "Tea", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a896", "question": "What city is home to the Milad Tower?", "answer": "Tehran", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6d8", "question": "Princeton University is located in which state?", "answer": "New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5bbd4d3c00d154d7af00b8d4", "question": "In the music video \"Opposites Attract\", what is the name of the cat Paula Abdul dances with?", "answer": "MC Skat Kat", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0c7", "question": "Who was the first American astronaut to orbit the Earth, circling it three times in 1962?", "answer": "John Glenn", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6b7", "question": "What \"g\" word do biologists use to describe a group of species with common characteristics?", "answer": "Genus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58dba141874c93a3298b2124", "question": "Caracas is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Venezuela", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a0", "question": "What movie starred Johnny Depp as Willy Wonka?", "answer": "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133902e", "question": "What Athenian comic poet wrote \"Lysistrata\"?", "answer": "Aristophanes", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b03", "question": "In \"Jurassic Park\", the park is located on an island off the coast of what country?", "answer": "Costa Rica", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba85", "question": "Who succeeded Tom Brokaw as anchor on NBC\u2019s Nightly News in 2004?", "answer": "Brian Williams", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59e6b84ffb6c85e9e634ff4e", "question": "What nationality is golfer Paul Azinger?", "answer": "American", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaf8", "question": "N'Djamena is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Chad", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "600cc2406de0eb824d4052e5", "question": "Norman Rockwell is the official artist of which state?", "answer": "Massachusetts -- He spent 25 years living in the Berkshires of Massachusetts.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be38", "question": "How many players are there in a standard men's field lacrosse team?", "answer": "Ten", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac6f", "question": "Which empire was the first empire in history?", "answer": "The Akkadians", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeef", "question": "Who commanded the English Fleet against the Spanish Armada in 1588?", "answer": "Admiral Charles Howard", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2bb", "question": "Which of Henry VIII's wives was married four times herself?", "answer": "Catherine Parr", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe36ce40ada16518afdc03e", "question": "What car company makes the Econoline van", "answer": "Ford", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7cb2b877e98cb97778a16", "question": "Acapulco is a city in which Mexican state?", "answer": "Guerrero", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af79", "question": "What did John Hancock sign in 1776?", "answer": "Declaration of Independence", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c23b", "question": "Which European city is served by Galileo Galilei Airport?", "answer": "Pisa", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2e0", "question": "What year did actor Arthur Stanley Jefferson die?", "answer": "1965", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3a4", "question": "Which is the most densely populated country in the world?", "answer": "Monaco", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe8f5b201dd7bf43be5e82a", "question": "What is the largest tree fruit in the world?", "answer": "Jackfruit", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3c6", "question": "What continent includes Iran?", "answer": "Asia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c216", "question": "Which country were the 1948 Winter Olympic Games?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a9a", "question": "In the children?s nursery rhyme, what comes next after ?Mary, Mary quite contrary??", "answer": "How does your garden grow?", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1c9", "question": "Which film featured the song \"Springtime for Hitler\"?", "answer": "The Producers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594a61b02ebb971c1417fb89", "question": "Who tells the stories in \"One Thousand and One Nights\"?", "answer": "Scheherazade", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b00f", "question": "The Northern Mariana Islands became a US territory during what war?", "answer": "World War II", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c19", "question": "According to Exodus, what is the first plague of Egypt?", "answer": "Water into blood", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a61b", "question": "What US city is located near Lackland Air Force Base?", "answer": "San Antonio", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fdab8480b8cce1e6fda7051", "question": "What is a Spanish canvas sandal decorated with rope called?", "answer": "Espadrille", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afed", "question": "Who was the US president at the end of the Great Depression?", "answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133976a", "question": "What is the name of the clown in It?", "answer": "Pennywise", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af63", "question": "What is the first known form of written communication, found in the Mesopotamian Valley?", "answer": "Cuneiform", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338909", "question": "Who wrote \"The Hunchback of Notre Dame\"?", "answer": "Victor Hugo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b34f", "question": "Who did Zola Budd trip in the 1984 Olympics?", "answer": "Mary Decker", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c74", "question": "Rupert Giles was the librarian-mentor on what popular TV show?", "answer": "Buffy the Vampire Slayer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8f7", "question": "Approximately how many acres is a baseball field?", "answer": "2", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a760", "question": "The Arc de Triumphe is to Paris, as the Brandenburg Gate is to what other European capital city?", "answer": "Berlin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5febb9ae7e83c707845b213e", "question": "What kind of milk is used in chevre cheese?", "answer": "Goat", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a266", "question": "Which dance classic did the group \"The Trammps\" bring us?", "answer": "Disco Inferno", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5b5", "question": "What relative of the raccoon is sometimes known as the cat-bear?", "answer": "The Panda", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2ac", "question": "Whose scary movie character has the real name of Charles Lee Ray?", "answer": "Chucky\u00a0", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecd3aeec223966ae8f88c7", "question": "Who was the first person to accrue ten Academy Award nominations for acting?", "answer": "Bette Davis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b7ffb3b3a3a814d89068c63", "question": "Who is considered the Father of English literature?", "answer": "Geoffrey Chaucer", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dbc", "question": "What holiday is celebrated with an aluminum pole, the Airing of Grievances, and Feats of Strength?", "answer": "Festivus", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394c6", "question": "Who did agent John Drake work for in \"Secret Agent\"?", "answer": "NATO", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601370831381754895396382", "question": "In the 1990 film \"Home Alone\", the fictitious film that Kevin watches, \"Angels with Filthy Souls\", is a homage to what real film?", "answer": "\"Angels with Dirty Faces\" -- It is a 1938 gangster film starring James Cagney and Pat O'Brien.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6988b20565ad31a57c734", "question": "Odysseus left home to fight in what war?", "answer": "Trojan War", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59029f7ecad1ec93f27df760", "question": "What fruits are fermented to make Perry?", "answer": "Pears", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea77dfff048f679a45abd0", "question": "What breed of domestic cat is known for swimming?", "answer": "Turkish Van", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c212", "question": "Which country were the 1928 Winter Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5f7", "question": "In which city is the world famous La Scala opera house?", "answer": "Milan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa2a", "question": "In what Australian state would you find Whyalla?", "answer": "South Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abb7", "question": "What was Malawi formerly known as?", "answer": "Nyasaland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3ba", "question": "Which is the fourth planet from the Sun?", "answer": "Mars", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6015e19afe83fe1f2a824b97", "question": "Why did the British Royal Navy attack French warships at Mers-el-Kebir?", "answer": "The French crews refused to surrender their ships when the British requested", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c46", "question": "Prior to becoming a rapper, what popular Canadian TV show did Drake star in?", "answer": "Degrassi: The Next Generation", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a48f", "question": "On the bank of which river does the Portuguese capital of Lisbon stand?", "answer": "The Tagus", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c84c", "question": "In what organ of the human body would you find the Eustachian tube?", "answer": "The ear", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b70", "question": "What city did the S.S. Minnow leave from on its three-hour tour on the original TV series \"Gilligan's Island\"?", "answer": "Honolulu", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a539", "question": "Which US state's highest mountain is Mt. Rainier?", "answer": "Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339db2", "question": "In the show \"Jackie Chan Adventures\", which antagonist turned into a protagonist after the show's first season?", "answer": "Tohru", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a674", "question": "Which state is located between Maine and Vermont?", "answer": "New Hampshire", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397bf", "question": "What does Marilyn Monroe say are a \"girl's best friend\" in Gentlemen Prefer Blondes?", "answer": "Diamonds", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58bb3414e368446ca7bd6849", "question": "What are the two most popular types of coffee beans?", "answer": "Arabica and Robusta", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58f5660b33a95c66dc4fe75d", "question": "Which British opera festival was started in 1934?", "answer": "Glyndebourne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59f9b7ca364247bf200fb876", "question": "Which Canadian city was originally called Bytown?", "answer": "Ottawa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58a0f5ea732c90c4fd3069cf", "question": "Who was the childhood playmate of little Jackie Papers?", "answer": "Puff, the Magic Dragon", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c30c", "question": "What is the molten rock magma called once it flows from a volcano?", "answer": "Lava", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe6a18120565ad31a57c7a4", "question": "What company was formerly named Cadabra Inc.?", "answer": "Amazon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393d4", "question": "What TV character's first spoken words were \"Goodbye kids\"?", "answer": "Clarabell the Clown", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339823", "question": "Who did Glen Campbell replace when the Beach Boys went on tour in 1965?", "answer": "Brian Wilson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c3f", "question": "What duo composed the operetta \"Porgy and Bess\"?", "answer": "George Gershwin and Ira Gershwin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9ac", "question": "In 1983, who became the first African American to win the Miss America Pageant?", "answer": "Vanessa Williams", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6010c6440775fa611bce67d0", "question": "Singapore's Marina Bay Sands hotel is home to the world's highest what?", "answer": "Swimming pool -- The hotel has on its rooftop an enormous infinity pool.  At 650 feet, it is the world's  highest swimming pool.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ded", "question": "What TV show's theme song was called \"The Fishin' Hole\"?", "answer": "The Andy Griffith Show", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391fb", "question": "Who played Vincent Vega in \"Pulp Fiction\"?", "answer": "John Travolta", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf7d", "question": "What's the opposite of the Orient?", "answer": "The Occident", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f9f4d44af848b908361b880", "question": "What year was the first color photograph taken?", "answer": "1861", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b373", "question": "What country's explorers discovered the site of Pensacola, Florida?", "answer": "Spain's", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fef5e106ce05a3942286e2f", "question": "Which movie\u2019s sequel has the tagline \"Same make. Same model. New mission\"?", "answer": "\"Terminator\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a9e96d27ccba3ffe45786f2", "question": "What is produced using the Kroll process?", "answer": "Metallic titanium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a06e", "question": "Who played Sandy in the made for TV adaptation of Grease Live?", "answer": "Julianne Hough", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf31", "question": "What event occurs at Walthamstow Stadium?", "answer": "Greyhound Racing", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4dd", "question": "What is the most mountainous country in Europe?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbc6", "question": "What popular soft drink claims to contain 23 flavors?", "answer": "Dr. Pepper", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a32f", "question": "What was the debut album of the band \"Belle and Sebastian\"?", "answer": "Tigermilk", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d5a", "question": "Who worked as a salesman at Gary's Shoes and Accessories?", "answer": "Al Bundy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dbe", "question": "What double-word song title was a hit single by The Archies?", "answer": "Sugar, Sugar", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339224", "question": "Who celebrated is 111th birthday during \"The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring?\"", "answer": "Bilbo Baggins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600242004be4723ccac22180", "question": "Which Irish poet, born in 1865, was instrumental in the founding of the Abbey Theatre in Dublin?", "answer": "William Butler Yeats", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5eb735e75e259d786908732a", "question": "What two men are considered the most notable two-time recepients of Congressional Medals of Honor?", "answer": "Smedley Butler and Dan Daly", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b686", "question": "Figure skater Elvis Stojko comes from which country?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59067d13ff9c0647b50a8072", "question": "Which film was the highest-grossing film of 2016?", "answer": "Captain America: Civil War", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd662c7a5bfecdd737e0848", "question": "What was Princess Diana's title before she married Prince Charles?", "answer": "Lady Diana Spencer", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5febba977e83c707845b2145", "question": "What was the first Super Bowl to use Roman numerals in its title?", "answer": "Super Bowl V", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a74", "question": "What was the name of the high school attended by Archie Andrews and his comic-book friends?", "answer": "Riverdale", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "60062afcc9d816e292245c1c", "question": "What American artist preferred to call his sculptures \"structures\"?", "answer": "Sol LeWitt\u00a0came to fame in the late 1960s with his wall drawings and \"structures\" but was prolific in a wide range of media.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff516dcff04d658268c92f6", "question": "Which organ was typically left in the body of mummies?", "answer": "Heart", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b997", "question": "On which racecourse in County Kildare are the 5 Irish Classics run?", "answer": "The Curragh", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffb5d605dad637d903c8823", "question": "What is the largest city in South America?", "answer": "S\u00e3o Paulo, Brazil", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a489", "question": "To which group of islands does Corfu belong?", "answer": "Ionian islands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ade8", "question": "In which decade was the word \"Internet\" coined?", "answer": "1980s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea7a68ff048f679a45abeb", "question": "The Arrector Pili muscles are responsible for what phenomenon?", "answer": "Goose bumps", "category": "science"}, {"id": "594d08ab1a1c922dd1ac64c5", "question": "\"My Ever Changing Moods\" was a hit for which UK band?", "answer": "The Style Council", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ca3c3c44f0f6af5b06662e", "question": "In which Shakespeare play does Launcelot Gobbo appear?", "answer": "The Merchant of Venice", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58f16829f7c52aae91cc07c3", "question": "What expression is used to describe a child who closely resembles a parent?", "answer": "Chip off the old block", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe69bed20565ad31a57c765", "question": "Who was the first U.S. senator to be elected president?", "answer": "James Monroe", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf0b", "question": "How many tiles does a player play to score a bingo in Scrabble?", "answer": "7", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7d037877e98cb97778a5d", "question": "Louisville, Kentucky sits on what river?", "answer": "Ohio", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ffa3bddc73aa70ea0b70ae9", "question": "Where is the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier located?", "answer": "Arlington National Cemetery, Virginia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339978", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", where was Lenny born?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909caddbb53d1af658864d3", "question": "What ABC Original Movie, starring Jenny McCarthy, air on December 10, 2006?", "answer": "Santa Baby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b08", "question": "What actor played the villain, Simon Gruber, in \"Die Hard with a Vengeance\"?", "answer": "Jeremy Irons", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5be", "question": "What is the largest salt-water lake in the US?", "answer": "Great Salt Lake", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133959f", "question": "What is Ace Ventura's occupation in the movies by the same name?", "answer": "Pet detective", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58dba39f874c93a3298b213e", "question": "Who was nicknamed La Pucelle d'Orl\u00e9ans?", "answer": "Joan of Arc", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb54", "question": "On what mountain does Moses speak to God through the burning bush and received the Ten Commandments?", "answer": "Mt. Sinai", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c9e7877e98cb977789fe", "question": "In Oaxaca, Mexico, Christmas Eve is also called \"Night of\" what vegetable?", "answer": "Radish", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abd8", "question": "The island country Cyprus lies south of what country?", "answer": "Turkey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f66", "question": "Who was the lead singer of the Sugarcubes?", "answer": "Bjork", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c68e", "question": "What element\u2019s chemical symbol is \"Ni\"?", "answer": "Nickel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf84", "question": "What is British politician William Hague's middle name?", "answer": "Jefferson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600cc4616de0eb824d4052f2", "question": "\"Jana Gana Mana\" is the national anthem of which Asian country?", "answer": "India", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133befd", "question": "How many players are there on a standard soccer team on field?", "answer": "11", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5bfdffe3b668d7dfe168b5bd", "question": "Chablis wine comes from which French wine region?", "answer": "Burgundy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339850", "question": "How many legs does the catbus have in \"My Neighbour Totoro\"?", "answer": "12", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6017401844491cbd7c5a17ba", "question": "Who was the only one of Henry VIII\u2019s wives to receive a Queen\u2019s funeral?", "answer": "Jane Seymour", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5a7", "question": "The city of Honolulu is located on what island?", "answer": "Oahu", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396da", "question": "What kind of wine does Hannibal Lecter recommend while enjoying a human liver?", "answer": "Chianti", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59bb2a0ec9bff04efae6d75b", "question": "Who had a No. 1 hit in 1965 with the song \"I'm Alive\"?", "answer": "The Hollies", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c54f", "question": "What is the name given to the animals that live their lives both in water and on land?", "answer": "Amphibians", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339483", "question": "What powers Monstropolis in the movie \"Monsters, Inc.\"?", "answer": "Screams", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe69fc820565ad31a57c790", "question": "Where did the \u201cwiki\u201d in Wikipedia come from?", "answer": "Hawaiian for \"fast\" or \"quick\"", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5bbd4f8a00d154d7af00b8d6", "question": "What are the names of the brothers in the band \"Right Said Fred\"?", "answer": "Fred and Richard Fairbrass", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a4a954861d1b4d384d5d677", "question": "What is pumpernickel?", "answer": "A type of German bread", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133896b", "question": "What is the better-known name of crime fiction writer Lady Mallowan D.B.E.?", "answer": "Agatha Christie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "591c3820815febcc896f927a", "question": "What is the ninth sign of the Zodiac?", "answer": "Sagittarius", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d8a", "question": "What original literary work was the movie \"The Heiress\" based on?", "answer": "Washington Square", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d1b", "question": "What German composer lost his hearing at the age of 20?", "answer": "Beethoven", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe65e611f3c0ead6880d62b", "question": "According to the Bible, which Apostle was a tentmaker?", "answer": "Paul", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395ed", "question": "In The Simpsons, who once attacked Lisa when she was cross-country skiing?", "answer": "Vicious deer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5cb70c57f96e155acab35d2b", "question": "Which planet in the Solar System has moons named after characters from Shakespeare's plays?", "answer": "Uranus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5a2", "question": "How many sides does a nonagon have?", "answer": "9", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acbe", "question": "What name was given to the leather protection cowboys wore over the front of their pants?", "answer": "Chaps", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6010c76d0775fa611bce67d9", "question": "Which organization publishes \"Boys\u2019 Life\" magazine?", "answer": "Boy Scouts of America", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b984", "question": "Which small guitar associated with George Formby was patented in Hawaii in 1917?", "answer": "Ukulele", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59f9bbd8364247bf200fb8a9", "question": "What country borders Zambia to the north?", "answer": "Congo", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5febbc977e83c707845b214e", "question": "How long did it take the director of the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\" to write the script?", "answer": "Eight weeks", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b616", "question": "What does \"Aardvark\" mean in Afrikaans?", "answer": "Earth pig", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a02", "question": "What Shakespeare play is set on January 5?", "answer": "Twelfth Night", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a531", "question": "What US city is located on the shores of Rapid Creek?", "answer": "Rapid City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5feddf166ce05a3942286dae", "question": "In which year was Tiger Woods named the PGA Tour Rookie of the Year?", "answer": "1996", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2ca", "question": "Sir Frances Walshingham was what English monarch's \"spy-master\"?", "answer": "Elizabeth I's", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5bbd52ea00d154d7af00b8db", "question": "Which band recorded the song \"Killing in the Name\"?", "answer": "Rage Against the Machine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "590678afff9c0647b50a804b", "question": "On what day of the week did January 1, 2016, fall?", "answer": "Friday", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5e3", "question": "What is the most common ending for a city, town, village or hamlet in England?", "answer": "-ton", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be21", "question": "George Fox is traditionally called the founder of what religious group?", "answer": "The Quakers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dfb", "question": "What \"Fantasy Island\" actor ended up committing suicide?", "answer": "Herve Villechaize", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5906834bff9c0647b50a80a5", "question": "What TV show, sequel to an ABC sitcom that ended in 1995, was released by Netflix on February 26, 2016?", "answer": "Fuller House", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba2b", "question": "In which US state is the General Sherman Tree located?", "answer": "California", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59f9b9a7364247bf200fb88f", "question": "The fear of shellfish is known as what?", "answer": "Ostraconophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133901a", "question": "Who painted the \"Rockeby Venus\"?", "answer": "Diego Velazquez", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1b6", "question": "Who played Steve Urkel in the TV show \"Family Matters\"?", "answer": "Jaleel White", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7f5", "question": "What Australian island is named for the man who circumnavigated Australia and discovered New Zealand?", "answer": "Tasmania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b69d", "question": "The name \"Otto\" is German for what?", "answer": "Wealth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ca4", "question": "According to his theme song, what is the most wonderful thing about Tiggers?", "answer": "I'm the only one", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd47", "question": "The US Army's elite 101st Airborne Division is known as the \"Screaming\" what?", "answer": "Eagles", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a354", "question": "What is the only US state that borders a Canadian territory?", "answer": "Alaska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6ef", "question": "Which US state is home to Joshua Tree National Park?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0a0", "question": "Happy Days was a spin off from what US TV show?", "answer": "Love American Style", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff7c1662b316f4693fb679d", "question": "Which famous sandwich was formerly known as the Blue Ribbon Burger?", "answer": "Big Mac", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59029feccad1ec93f27df766", "question": "What country does the cappuccino originate from?", "answer": "Italy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5990b018b72eedf883a8c70f", "question": "In what country do people speak the language they call Nihongo?", "answer": "Japan", "category": "arts"}]